let questions = [{"numb": 1, "question": "Ahnung", "answer": "Assumption", "options": ["Operation,", "Wastage", "Assumption", "Backward"]}, {"numb": 2, "question": "Abfall", "answer": "Wastage", "options": ["Wastage", "expired", "Triangle", "buildings"]}, {"numb": 3, "question": "Verlauf", "answer": "process", "options": ["trip, Clue, Sulivu", "Judgement", "forward", "process"]}, {"numb": 4, "question": "Betrieb", "answer": "Operation,", "options": ["process", "Operation,", "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu"]}, {"numb": 5, "question": "H\u00e4ufig", "answer": "Frequently", "options": ["Contract", "Sideways", "Frequently", "buildings"]}, {"numb": 6, "question": "Leitung", "answer": "Leadership, Conduct", "options": ["Details ,  Kannada : dattamsha", "Rectangular", "Triangle", "Leadership, Conduct"]}, {"numb": 7, "question": "Vorw\u00e4rts", "answer": "forward", "options": ["forward", "Weather, Kannada: Havaamaana", "Operation,", "Task"]}, {"numb": 8, "question": "Schrifft", "answer": "Script", "options": ["Frequently", "Triangle", "buildings", "Script"]}, {"numb": 9, "question": "knapp", "answer": "almost kannada: durlabha, virala, saakagada", "options": ["trip, Clue, Sulivu", "Talent", "almost kannada: durlabha, virala, saakagada", "Rectangular"]}, {"numb": 10, "question": "Angabe", "answer": "Details ,  Kannada : dattamsha", "options": ["Details ,  Kannada : dattamsha", "Backward", "Judgement", "Contract"]}, {"numb": 11, "question": "Vertrag", "answer": "Contract", "options": ["Task", "Contract", "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu", "Operation,"]}, {"numb": 12, "question": "Aufgabe", "answer": "Task", "options": ["Task", "Suit, Costume", "Wastage", "expired"]}, {"numb": 13, "question": "Urteil", "answer": "Judgement", "options": ["Judgement", "Suit, Costume", "process", "Talent"]}, {"numb": 14, "question": "Ablauf", "answer": "expired", "options": ["Leadership, Conduct", "forward", "expired", "Container"]}, {"numb": 15, "question": "Anzug", "answer": "Suit, Costume", "options": ["Triangle", "Suit, Costume", "Leadership, Conduct", "Container"]}, {"numb": 16, "question": "Mangel", "answer": "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "options": ["Rectangular", "buildings", "Leadership, Conduct", "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)"]}, {"numb": 17, "question": "Ruckw\u00e4rts", "answer": "Backward", "options": ["Backward", "expired", "Triangle", "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)"]}, {"numb": 18, "question": "Geb\u00e4ude", "answer": "buildings", "options": ["Wastage", "process", "Contract", "buildings"]}, {"numb": 19, "question": "Seitew\u00e4rts", "answer": "Sideways", "options": ["Triangle", "Sideways", "Container", "Leadership, Conduct"]}, {"numb": 20, "question": "Dreieck", "answer": "Triangle", "options": ["forward", "Contract", "Triangle", "Script"]}, {"numb": 21, "question": "Gabe", "answer": "Talent", "options": ["Talent", "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "trip, Clue, Sulivu", "expired"]}, {"numb": 22, "question": "Hinweise", "answer": "trip, Clue, Sulivu", "options": ["trip, Clue, Sulivu", "Suit, Costume", "Judgement", "Script"]}, {"numb": 23, "question": "Wesentlich", "answer": "Crucial", "options": ["trip, Clue, Sulivu", "Rectangular", "buildings", "Crucial"]}, {"numb": 24, "question": "Gewitter", "answer": "Weather, Kannada: Havaamaana", "options": ["Triangle", "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "buildings", "Weather, Kannada: Havaamaana"]}, {"numb": 25, "question": "kreis", "answer": "circle", "options": ["Suit, Costume", "trip, Clue, Sulivu", "Container", "circle"]}, {"numb": 26, "question": "Vierecke", "answer": "Rectangular", "options": ["circle", "Rectangular", "process", "Task"]}, {"numb": 27, "question": "Behalter", "answer": "Container", "options": ["trip, Clue, Sulivu", "circle", "Container", "Assumption"]}, {"numb": 28, "question": "bedinungen", "answer": "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu", "options": ["trip, Clue, Sulivu", "process", "Triangle", "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu"]}];